http://www.alliance1.org/web/terms-use.aspx

Skip to main content
Loading
Skip breadcrumb navigation
Alliance Home Page
»
Terms of Use
1. Acceptance of Terms. By using this website you agree to be bound by these “Terms of Use.”
2. Definitions. The “Website” means any websites owned or operated by the Alliance for Strong Families and Communities and its affiliates, including FEI Behavioral Health, and Ways to Work (the “Alliance”), including, but not limited to, the websites operated at the domain names www.alliance1.org, www.feinet.com, and www.waystowork.org.
3. Use of the Site. The Alliance operates the Websites to provide member services, library and data repositories, educational services and information relevant to users of our Websites or members of the Alliance. Any new features added to the Websites will also be subject to these Terms of Use.
4. Member Account, Password and Security. If you create an account on the Websites or become a member of the Alliance on the Websites, you will receive a password and account designation upon completing the registration process. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the password and account, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. You agree to: (a) provide true, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the registration or profile form (your “Registration Data”); (b) maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it true, current and complete; (c) immediately notify the Alliance of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security; and (d) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. The Alliance has the right to suspend or terminate your account for any reason, including for violations of this or any other agreement with the Alliance. Any Personal Data in your Registration Data will be collected, used and disclosed as provided in our Privacy Policy.
5. Site Content. The content on the Websites, except all User Content (as defined below), including without limitation, the trademarks, copyrighted material, text, software, graphics, templates, photos, music, videos, and the like (“Site Content”), is owned by or licensed to the Alliance and is subject to trademark, copyright and other intellectual property laws of the United States and foreign countries. You shall not retain, copy, publish, distribute, use or edit any Site Content or any portion of Site Content except as expressly allowed through use of the Websites during the term of this or any other agreement with us. For example, you may not retain, copy, publish, distribute, use or edit any materials prepared by or distributed by the Alliance after the term of this agreement or after termination of any account you may have with us. The Alliance reserves the right to add to, delete from, or modify any part of the Site Content at any time without notice.
6. User Content. You may be able to post user-generated content, such as articles, messages, notes, information, photos, policies, business documents, discussions, blog posts, and ratings (“User Content”) on the Websites. You will remain the owner of the User Content. By posting User Content, you grant the Alliance an irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, transferable, fully paid, worldwide license (with the right to sublicense) to use, copy, publicly perform, publicly display, reformat, edit, translate, excerpt (in whole or in part), publish, and distribute such User Content for any purpose, commercial, advertising, or otherwise, on or in connection with the Alliance, the Websites or the promotion thereof, to prepare derivative works of, or incorporate into other works, such User Content, and to grant and authorize sublicenses of the foregoing. By posting User Content, you represent and warrant that you have the right to post the User Content, that no third party rights will be violated by such posting, and that you have the right to grant the Alliance the rights granted herein. In posting User Content, you further agree that you shall not post any personal information belonging to another person, nor any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, slanderous, inflammatory, pornographic or profane material, material promoting a political agenda, or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense. You agree not to post User Content for any commercial purpose without the express written permission of the Alliance. Posting of JavaScript or other code, files or programs that interfere with this site’s operations is strictly prohibited. The posting of certain types of User Content may link to or require the use of a third party, such as a blog facilitator or a social media account; the Alliance has no responsibility for any interaction between you and a third party. The Alliance has the right to deny posting of, or to remove, any User Content, for any reason, at any time.
7. Fees. If you have signed up for a membership, service, or an account for which fees apply, you agree to the fees, time periods, and payment terms posted on the Websites for the services you have selected at the time you enrolled in such services. Such services may include certain packages, subscriptions, and other offerings that may be added to the Websites in the future. If you cancel any services or the account with which you use certain services, your payments are not refundable unless a different cancellation policy is identified for the particular Service you are using.
8. Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy governs the collection, use and disclosure of all Personal Data (personally identifiable information about you, such as your full name, birth date, email address or mailing address, phone number and any other information that can be used to identify or contact you). For more information, see our full privacy policy at alliance1.org/alliance/privacy-policy.
9. Third Party Intellectual Property. The Alliance respects the intellectual property rights of others. We will respond promptly to remove material that infringes another person’s copyright or other intellectual property right. Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (17 U.S.C. §512(c)(2)), our designated agent to receive notices of claimed infringement is: severson@alliance1.org.
10. Websites Provided “As Is.” You understand and agree that the Websites and all services and information provided on it are provided “As Is” and that the Alliance assumes no responsibility for the accuracy, timeliness, deletion or mis-delivery of any user communication,
information, or configuration. You, and not the Alliance, are entirely responsible for all material that you post, transmit or otherwise make available through the Websites. The Alliance does not review or control all of the material that others post, transmit or otherwise make available through the Websites, and accordingly the Alliance does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such material. You acknowledge that the Alliance and its designees shall have the right (but not the obligation) in their sole discretion to refuse or remove any material that is available through the Websites, including all User Content.
11. Indemnification. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless the Alliance, and its board members, committee members, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, and employees, from any claim or demand by any third party arising out of material you post, transmit or otherwise make available through the Websites, your use of the Websites, your connection to the Websites, your violation of these Terms of Use, or your violation of any rights of another person or entity.
12. DISCLAIMER.
THE WEBSITES, INCLUDING ANY CONTENT OR INFORMATION CONTAINED WITHIN OR PROVIDED THROUGH IT, IS PROVIDED “AS IS” WITH NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT. YOU ASSUME TOTAL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THEWEBSITES AND THE INFORMATION RECEIVED THROUGH THEM. FURTHER,
THE ALLIANCE MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS WHATSOEVER ABOUT OTHER WEBSITES WHICH YOU MAY ACCESS THROUGH THIS WEBSITE. THE ALLIANCE FURTHER DOES NOT WARRANT THE QUALITY, VALIDITY, ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE MATERIALS OR THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED ON THE WEBSITES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, OR THAT DEFECTS OR INACCURACIES WILL BE CORRECTED. THE ALLIANCE MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THE WEBSITES, OR TO THE PRODUCTS, SERVICES, SPECIFICATIONS OR PRICES DESCRIBED IN IT, AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE. THE MATERIALS MAY BE OUT OF DATE, AND THE ALLIANCE MAKES NO COMMITMENT TO UPDATE THE MATERIALS AT THE WEBSITES OR TO MAKE ANY NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES.
INFORMATION PUBLISHED AT THE WEBSITES MAY REFER TO PRODUCTS, PROGRAMS OR SERVICES THAT ARE NOT AVAILABLE.
13. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.
THE ALLIANCE AND ITS BOARD MEMBERS, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES AND AGENTS AND ITS AFFILIATES ARE NEITHER RESPONSIBLE NOR LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE OR OTHER DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING IN ANY WAY TO THE WEBSITES OR ANY INFORMATION RECEIVED FROM THE WEBSITES, INCLUDING THE CONTENT OR ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED WITHIN OR THROUGH THE WEBSITES. YOUR SOLE REMEDY FOR DISSATISFACTION WITH THE WEBSITES IS TO STOP USING THE WEBSITES AND THE INFORMATION OBTAINED THEREIN.
14. Miscellaneous. These Terms of Use and the relationship between you and the Alliance shall be governed by the laws of the State of Wisconsin. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the federal and state courts located in the State of Wisconsin for all purposes in connection with any action or proceeding which arises out of or relates to your use of the Websites, these Terms of Use, or any Content, Personal Data, User Content, or Registration Data. The Alliance’s failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms of Use does not constitute a waiver of that right or provision. The Alliance may revise these Terms of Use at any time, and any such revisions shall be effective immediately without notice. You should visit this page from time to time to review the then-current Terms of Use. The Alliance may, in its sole discretion, terminate or suspend your access to all or part of the Websites for any reason, including, without limitation, breach of these Terms of Use.
Effective Date: May 11, 2016
15360222.5
{1}
##LOC[OK]##
{1}
##LOC[OK]##
##LOC[Cancel]##
{1}
